(Sheldon:)Since we got home
from the comic bookstore.
(Leonard:)That was two hours ago.
(Sheldon:)As per your suggestion,
(Sheldon:)we're hanging out.
(Sheldon:)Quite frankly, I don't see
(Sheldon:)what all the hoopla's about.
(Sheldon:)Go on, Amy.
(Amy:)From a neurobiological
standpoint, Leonard,
(Amy:)you may be alone
because your psychological state
(Amy:)is causing
an actual pheromone-based stink
(Amy:)of desperation.
(Sheldon:)Did you know that, Leonard?
(Sheldon:)No.
I did.
Leonard, I understand
that some people find mates
(Amy:)in social gathering places
such as bars or taverns.
(Amy:)Have you tried a bar or tavern?
(Leonard:)No, I'm not gonna try
to pick up a woman in a bar.
(Sheldon:)Wise decision. You see, Amy,
(Sheldon:)success at a bar is based
on classic male attributes
(Sheldon:)such as height, strength,
attractiveness,
(Sheldon:)the ability to hold one's liquor
and throw darts--
(Sheldon:)separately or together.
(Sheldon:)Leonard has none of these
attributes, right, Leonard?
(Leonard:)Right.
(Amy:)That's not true of all bars.
(Amy:)Juice bars, for example.
(Sheldon:)Oh! Good point, Amy.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, building
on your premise,